http://www.arkcls.com/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyIntroductionThis Privacy Notice represents the full online Privacy Policy applicable to ARK CLS Ltd’s online activities.  It will explain the types of data ARK CLS collects and how it is used.  Our website is governed in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).  ARK CLS understand that you care about your privacy and take that very seriously.  ARK CLS recognise that keeping your personal information private is an ongoing responsibility, and pledge to update this Privacy Notice whenever we adopt new privacy policies or add new personal data practices. Data Protection OfficerThe data controller responsible for your personal information for the purposes of the applicable GDPR is:ATTN:  Data Protection Officer ARK CLS Ltd Bedford i-Lab Priory Business Park Stannard Way Bedford   MK44 3RZ United Kingdom Telephone: +44 1234 834864 e-mail:  info@arkcls.comIf you have any questions about this Privacy Notice or our data collection practices, please contact us at the address, telephone or e-mail listed above and specify your country of residence and the nature of your question.Collection of Personal DataMost of the information on our website is available without having to release your personal data.  You are also able to enter a limited amount of required data when requesting evaluations, support etc.  This information is necessary to collect however you can opt-out of receiving marketing communications at any time.All our online request forms require your first name, last name, company name and e-mail – we need to gather this information to be able to respond to your request.Sharing of Personal DataPersonal data will only be shared with third parties when it is necessary in relation to providing services.  We would only share the necessary information in these circumstances and will not disclose your data to any third parties for the purpose of marketing.Data Storage and RetentionPersonal data is stored by ARK CLS Ltd on its servers and cloud based servers.  Your data is only retained for as long as it is necessary for the intended purpose.Data Subject RightsYou have the right to access your personal data, as well as rectifying it or removing it at any time.  ARK CLS will only include you our mailing list if you have agreed and will able to opt out of any e-mail communications at any time.Verifying your identityWhere you request access to your information, we are required by law to use all reasonable measures to verify your identity before doing so.These measures are designed to protect your information and to reduce the risk of identity fraud, identity theft or general unauthorised access to your information.Web server log informationWe use a third party server to host our website called Digital Ocean, the privacy policy of which is available here:  https://www.digitalocean.com/legal/privacy-policy/Our website server automatically logs the IP address you use to access our website as well as other information about your visit such as the pages accessed, information requested, the date and time of the request, [the source of your access to our website (e.g. the website or URL (link) which referred you to our website), and your browser version and operating system.Use of website server log information for IT security purposesOur third party hosting provider collect(s) and store(s) server logs to ensure network and IT security and so that the server and website remain uncompromised. This includes analysing log files to help identify and prevent unauthorised access to our network, the distribution of malicious code, denial of services attacks and other cyber attacks, by detecting unusual or suspicious activity.Unless we are investigating suspicious or potential criminal activity, we do not make, nor do we allow our hosting provider to make, any attempt to identify you from the information collected via server logs.SecurityARK CLS is committed to taking appropriate technical, physical and organisational measures to protect Personal Data against unauthorised access, unlawful processing, accidental loss or damage and unauthorsied destruction etc.Questions or ComplaintsPlease contact ARK CLS Ltd’s Data Protection Officer with any questions or complaints.Back to top
This site uses cookies to improve your experience. Read more.No problem
